# Crying and laughing Every use the stars illuminate Dance floor
(If it's with you, I'm invincible, this moment)
♪ With you, I'm invincible, this moment
It's surprisingly cold.
Laughter
But, you know, the floor, you can still see it.
It's still frozen.
Is it early this morning?
Early morning?
Yes, sir.
But you're okay?
Yes, but I'm fine.
But I'm fine.
Surprisingly, yes.
Now, with the Nara Sash and all, the dance scene is the scariest.
And at night, there's a Hortolate out there.
I'm thinking, "Who's Hortolate? I was thinking.
Â The stars are shining and the dance full is...
Â™" I wish I could be with you.
♪ Right now, at this moment ♪
Me.
It was more than I imagined. More than I imagined.
Come here, please.
Look! It's so high when the door is closed.
Maybe I wasn't wrong about the hole.
Hey, open up.
There, there, there.
That's the door to get in.
I finished my book first. Sorry about that.
So look.
No, no, no.
Look.
All right, let's go!
Yes!
Thank you very much. It's done.
It's cold, but it was so warm in there.
Good night.
I'm sweet today, so I'm turning down the heat.
Have you seen the first episode of the second season of Maishul?
Only those who have seen it can understand.
I can't tell.
It's cold.
It snowed today. Actually.
Today's shooting.
Indeed. I'm glad it didn't snow today.
I'm really glad it didn't happen yesterday.
I'm glad.
It was recording for my last album,
After recording, I finally went outside and it was raining so hard,
I was thinking of not going home yet.
But when I opened the door a little while later, it was snowing like crazy,
I said, "Let's go home.
You were thinking of leaving in the snow?
I said I was going home in the snow.
The opposite. What is it? This way?
This way.
Today, I'm shooting a music video for Twinkle Wink.
We have shot 3 music videos for this album, and this is the last one,
We're filming at a place with a really cute set.
It's really cold today, so I'm going to dance a lot in the dance scenes to warm up.
I will do my best!
I really like dancing in this "Twinkle Wink",
There are a lot of difficult sound frames that I have never seen before,
This "Twinkle Wink" represents tears,
I don't know if it's tears or not, but it's so cute. I don't know,
I don't know, but I really like the cute, pop, catchy choreography,
The choreography of the chorus is also difficult,
The choreography of the chorus is difficult, but I hope you will dance along with me.
Yay!
I'm not laughing.
Yes, cut!
Thank you for your hard work.
Good night
And here we go.
That was Yamawashi.
Good night.
I'm having fun.
It was fun.
Really?
I'm sure.
Emma was standing next to me.
I'm laughing.
You were laughing?
The thing that hit me the hardest was...
Yuna was taking the main picture
And in the portlet behind her...
Like this all the time.
Yuna's face
I don't know what to do
She was making this really nice face.
She's blurring behind me.
She's shaking her head.
I'm wearing two hair-tags
I don't know how to get them together.
Uh...
I don't know how we're gonna be together.
What the fuck?
Two minutes for this
2 minutes
It wasn't this.
what the hell is this?
This was before.
I thought you said there were two.
Which one was it?
That one? And this one.
That one?
That one? Which one was it?
That one? I thought you said they were the same.
Oh, it's a big one.
One. - Here.
This one.
I don't remember them being this different size.
This one?
Yeah.
Another one?
This one?
This one.
Oh, this one.
The last in the trilogy?
Yes.
We shot a lot of music videos this time.
I went for a high tone in my hair.
At the very end.
I think this music video will be very precious.
I hope you will see it a lot.
It's going to be fun!